how to attract a man who ignores you
sensation game existed from the
session after the killed seductive as it is
They even talk about his race as director of the
blog as a script to conquer a woman
dotcom in today's video we are going to
talk about how to surprise a woman
I have learned a secret to impress
or surprise the women I'm going to
share with you right now that
secret he knows that my name will be given
counts for itself
[Music]
for importers who, as you are,
Today I'm going to talk to you about 6 ways
fantastic nightclubs
Hello, I'm Hector Latorre. Today we're going to
talking about flirting in clubs is a big deal to me
You have asked many times, I will give you 6
tricks 6 ways 6 techniques that you should
apply before yours
the first and another the 1
I like your friend 7 is something very special
for her but you don't know what to say or what
do when you're with her because
You're scared, well, I understand you.
situation and the first thing is that I accept it
the fact that you are a virgin we have all
been virgins at some point some
continue to be so but that is not a
problem we have all been at some point
moment of our life we are actually born
being virgins so accept it in itself
She is your friend with the background you feel
that she is something more to you but not
you know if she feels the same way about you and
that anxiety
[Music]
last
that I'm in what you want
[Music]
Sorry girls, do you know where it is?
bathroom
over there
I tell you that I don't have any balls.
ask Lewis what today for
the morning seen that he is looking in the
small room of material
Girls, if you come looking for someone, this
It was Lewis and this was my dog
who ate it
Hello friend Nasa, everything and well, let's go
learn how to open a coconut left
Yeah
oh sorry
GOOD
Coach, do you know where the kitchen is?
I need a knife, something to pass.
the kitchen
[Music]
seems
that I have lost myself wherever I can is because
it's faster there
go go
and there I lost
to go back
and
[Music]
Hey, could you tell me where the
nearest bathroom
looking for the nearest bathroom starting the route
located in the hallway
today is to go and here now I have the exam
tomorrow
the exam started at half an hour
later
[Music]
because if you can tell me the grade of the
statistics exam
but the teacher recommends that you do it
use more colored plastics for the
exams
you should start using a pen
today is to go and the exam is suspended
Can you call my mother please?
adding lentils to the list of
buy
today is to go and here now I have to go to the
hair salon
You now have seven to go
butt waxing
Siri is serious, now I have to go.
to the hairdresser
today is to say how can I pass the
economics exam
I don't think you have a chance of
pass that exam called mind matrix
go home you're wasting your time here
mom mom who just told me yes that
No, I don't approve, okay, I'm going home.
I pass my water, strength that I can't take anymore
[Music]
I'm going to tell you where the bathroom is.
nearby
looking for the nearest bathroom
starting route located in corridor 3
meters turn right
continue straight for 20 meters to the right
in the advanced and lower physics section
the stairs
molecular biology
while
is lost
It's that I would go to Diego, I'm not going to give in
turns around here
today is to go and how the integral is calculated
indefinite of 3x squared between
logarithm of 6x to 3
if you hadn't spent all night
playing strongly you wouldn't know
Please continue, I have to deliver.
the work in a few hours also
answer
I'm tired of you asking me
nonsense all day
I know that these are not nonsense that I have to
submit the work or not
[Music]
today is to go and it could be that I am
going bald
I have analyzed a photo of your father and
I reckon you're going to go bald in
less than a year
congratulations
but active
I hope you are well
[Music]
or not
today is going and someone has burned my
Philosophy notes: What can I do?
you should start praying I don't think so
accident
today is going and I have lost the notes of
thermodynamics you know where they can be
You don't need them, you're very smart.
thank you
It was sarcasm when you can be canine
that he
before
[Music]
if you want a math exam
Let's prove that it won't be right now
economy
who left me the notes here
by hand
in half an hour no more
you have little time to study for a
exam make a few notes and
summaries are vital to take advantage of
Diarra, not all of us have been in this situation.
situation some mind although studying
for unix 10 ways to attract a
girl without saying a word
impress the girl you like with
poetic phrases and compliments Avilés is not
the simplest task today
but surprisingly not many people
knows that attraction often occurs
before the words are
exchange and that does not mean that
you have to be the most handsome daddy of
the block
Hello, I am making this video for you and for
of
that you don't know how to put on a washing machine but if
you know how to dirty your clothes by finding them
You can't find clean clothes because
because you don't know how to put a washing machine on
The first thing you have to do is put the
little clothes
presentable are used chosen by the
individual
[Music]
welcome
In today's video I will show you six
brilliant ideas to copy in a
exam copy like a bottle uses one
bottle that is on some colored ribbons
not transparent after in a small
paper written with the function you want
very low
life hacks to make your crab fall in love with you
love and is currently single or
singles
just try not to give him such a look
strong as you might scare him a little
the effective people they carry inside and
start researching what kind of music
you listen to your favorite movies
food you like can also be
study your prey so that you can then attack
to whom they want to take the important step
with this person
[Music]
Hello everyone, in this tutorial I am going to tell you
explain how you should put a
dishwasher although in general the
dishwashers are usually different but
more or less have the same mentioned
before placing the dishes you should
pass them a little water and see that they don't
are excessively dirty once
you have the dishwasher full and ready
to put what is to put the pill
of the leaf
connected
thanks to what a shame
Manuel who says that you don't have to fill out
therefore because if not it floods
[Music]
once we are and respect each other like this
Welcome to long live the kitchen
and today we are going to prepare a rice with
milk in the purest traditional style
But let's see a simple trick to
that it becomes creamier
when you add the shells of the
citrus fruits remember to add the part
white that you are seized more than one
tax increase'
Have you ever felt better or something?
You see the ugly but trapped in that area
intermediate where you are not but none
person
suddenly she doesn't know why but
you look like a 10
how to chat with a woman
you can follow me
I'm going up
the light swimming
Now we're going fishing
with the topic of the day
success has the conversation of
but intense avoids
and things
and
[Music]
it sounds serious
is
oysters
new potatoes
i
now he's busy I'm wrong but no
I'm at the wrong table, I'm there
the
GOOD
[Music]
as
and neither
[Music]
ah
very low
TRUE
[Music]
[Applause]
today you go
or not
[Music]
sometimes
no no
i
hello
ah
that he didn't find the contact lens and
hello
don't worry about being me
encyclopedia
and
directly
no
Hey series, I have a lump on my
nearest hospital please
If someone goes to work tomorrow
that his son be dowried
don't fuck with me it's true
today is go and you can read the last one
message from my mother
will be wrong
today is going and I have broken a leg
where there is a hospital
[Music]
thank you
today is to go and how can I find a girlfriend
if you hear me go and I'm up to [ __ ] of
that you wake me up at seven in the morning
Please change my alarm.
They are also sisters
today is going and my [ __ ] hurts a lot
what I do
If my dog has escaped, how can I?
find it
vivo
type 2 people 2 where these people
parks
son of the guy where he is like that in the
park in this park
today is to go and because Andrea has left me
but furniture
today is going and they stole my wallet
call the civil guard
and looking for the best Chinese restaurant
nearby
today is go and send this message to me
mother
Today, mom, please let me sleep at home.
tonight I'm tired of sleeping
In the park my back hurts a lot
back please
think about it
better than him
today is going and I have a lump
Stranger from the ass calls a hospital for
favor
[Music]
My tongue is swollen, what can I do?
do
[Applause]
today is to go and how can I hide a fart
stretching
further
So
today is to go and how can I find a girlfriend
It would be like finding a job
it would be like [ __ ] in an ordinary
today is go and send this message to johnny
You see, I'm up to my [ __ ] ears in my
Mother God won't let me play formal and
It doesn't let me play, I'm not here, I'm going to leave
I didn't want to tell you anything about home anymore, let's see
If you let me sleep at your house for a few days
because I can't
message to johnny no mama there is a y
Today is the day and I haven't even broken my leg.
where there is a hospital
you have foreplay
50 meters from a state hospital
So they should withdraw the charges that live in
a hospital
alfonso xi
Be careful this afternoon, I don't know if you
They have counted but here come those of
health and there are inspections
how are you with the kitchen rats
and you cut them down because I don't want even a rat
Why is it that they close us? Hello, good ones
Yes, sir Alfredo, I'll call from pizza.
rib
If you have a little problem that
arriving home he gets hooked or the
motorcycle wheel on the curb and
the mailbox was smashed if it was more than anything
comment yes yes it was me
if the window also if the blood is
mine if now I go to the hospital
Yes, yes, I'll give you the pizzas for free, I don't know.
Worry if he leaves I'll go there
OK
So I was delivering some pizzas and
cows and a man and nation tire in
the head
Let me pass because I have a
man and I don't know anything
give me the blessings or I'll destroy you and of course
gives pizzas like Ximena burst the
my head is broken
It wasn't a very big tire but it is
that a head throws it away with the days
which
and look, it has stopped me again
civil guard
if the same place is always put
same place
at 180 but don't worry that's it
Maybe I've given the breathalyzer test
negative
but don't listen to one thing you buy
I'm going to be without a scooter for a while.
[ __ ] the motorcycle but if you buy a scooter
I can continue working at the company
agreement
If I'm going to recover Carmen, I don't know.
worry boss
If you look carefully at how you handle the issue of
All rats must be killed because
They're closing the bar on us.
If you hello good morning yes look for
report some events that happened to me
This morning the Civil Guard did look at that
I am a pizza delivery man, I was going for the
avenue to rebollo here near
mcdonald's near mcdonald's in
Tarragona and look how close I am to one
Grandma threw me off the motorcycle and
I have been beaten with the cane
leg burst come on it's that no no me
I can't even move it was to report it if
on top of that, two pizzas have been stolen.
I have a lot of work here and mother
mine if the ID 48 533
It's that my leg is broken
according to the girl who was in the
bathroom
on the ground
It is full of Mercadona and made the
change I think that the clients have not
tried and I don't know if which I think is
Yes, if we don't make ourselves exposed, it's not worth it.
the same price as always for several
You ask what is cocoa then?
Now I do come from the client.
she always leaves her hair loose and she arrived
to his house and the dog bit me all over
The bowling alley is that it always leaves it loose
If you bring me the cream, I'll put it on.
It always looks good even if it can't even
walk you know that I fit the bite
between the eggs
Hello, how are you? Yes, I'm working. Look.
since one thing that I have fallen from the
motorcycle and it has broken down, let's see if I
you can leave the wheelchair is that
I have to finish today's deliveries
and if I have used them I have used more
once in the wheelchair it's okay but
leave me because I have to finish
deliveries and look what it has
problem and will deliver more pizzas and
entered the playground you know the
from there you see that he skidded with the motorcycle
and I've been busted on the swings
the kids are exactly the ones to look at
there is some child hurt because if we want
I have to go quickly to deliver the
pizzas if you you see running because yes
I have you okay is running with him
Manolo's distribution, yes, I have fallen from the
motorcycle hits me a car but I have his
registration in we reported it yes yes I
I'm fine, I'm watching, look with the
rolls in the face but it hasn't happened to me
nothing happened and perfectly
Yes, yes, I'm fine, I'm fine, look at that.
I can run and do everything, you know if not?
I have no problem but boss people
Please don't fire me
but let's see people that I haven't eaten
pizza yo
Well yes, he ate a piece of me but it's just that
See, I ate the whole pizza but
is that he was starving to death
you make them work eight hours straight
pizzeria arrivals tell me
would be my knight
like there's a cockroach in the pizza
can't be a man
Let's see, we fumigated the premises a week ago.
It can't be that there is a cockroach in it
the pizza, let's see, send a photo because it's very
big or as he is he cannot be a gentleman
let's see what yes and look at a grandmother
He came running up and threw his hand at me.
Moto has hit me with his cane
is that I have a broken leg, it was for
Reporting it is what I am most exhausted about.
I have a pimple, let's say it's not that
They don't give me a car, the DNI is 48 cm.
not like my tooth was
Hello, good afternoon, yes it is here
Sandra, if you're in the office now
You know where I am because I am another
time going to burger king to [ __ ] because
I'm fed up with Juanjo
Juanjo had such a hard time clogging the toilet.
calls to maintenance
Let's see, this is the third time I have
that go to Burger King at [ __ ] this
week is that juanjo I know that he eats but
It can't be that the bathroom is
out of service every day
because it is the fifth time since juanjo
clogs the toilet and we're going to get out with the
windows already open them already because I have
that we should return to the office now and not
I want to meet there, let's go, it's that
and we are already with the same story of
Always check with Damian if there are any chairs missing.
the office that is what helps me go to
buy more chairs okay we're doing very well
bad budget that I'm not going to buy
more chairs that's why I buy them big
two people in a chair is already the
first rule of the office according to
see in this law firm you have to
share things, that is, we share
the chairs and everything okay yes yes yes
There is a lack of people who sit down, because you
you sit on the floor that there are studies that
They show that sitting on the floor is
good for the back the first thing is
Amia's health does not hear a thing
in the [ __ ] tell Luis to get out of
my chair
go out and see Javier is not going to go to the
university savings for the
Javier University, we'll remove them, okay?
because he has been repeating a year for two years and
Javier is not going to go to university, let's see.
Grandma's pension is also taken away
I need to invest pain please
I'm telling you now I'm going to go home and I'm going to
take out the money we have in the
freezer
for those who need to invest is that in
Seriously, Island is our chance.
of life to see bursting through the walls of
house where we keep cash hello
Good afternoon, is this the Starbucks?
Sant Ramon Street and look where I came from
Here for a moment I ordered a coffee but
without milk and here I see milk without the
videos without milk coffee while I
I'm saving the ocean turtles
you are polluting with the
milk cartons because this
It pollutes a lot, you don't know, I don't look
for the good of all then I am
saving dolphins, turtles and fish and
you in Benaissa the people with the
milk okay and I told you without
sugar is that I am diabetic
I told you saccharine, I'm going to live 150
years
It's not like I'm going to come back and you're going to
give a couple of cookies or if not
advertisements
You know, Juan Carlos from Human Resources.
don't go to the office, you've thrown everything away
the firecrackers that he had stored in the
syrupy box office throw in the trash because
He tells me that it is due to risk issues
work and you can't have everything
firecrackers in the office
So if Barça wins, what do I do?
What pisses me off is that if you don't like him here
to you too it is that it is that I am
going to the firecracker store I'm going to
[ __ ] the biggest firecracker there is and
I'm going to break the mailbox, Susana Díaz.
Lewis that until the report is finished
that they leave the office what I
It doesn't matter if his mother is in the
hospital I'm going to the hospital now to
check that your mother is sick
true okay I'll see because if it comes back
It's going to be one of these heart attacks.
I'm going to the hospital to see if your mother was there.
If you see, I have received an invoice
from the child's school
That is, he started breaking chairs a month ago.
that we signed him up for karate and I don't know what
how long ago
Listen to one thing, it's not that we're going to
to give is to aim in martial arts
This is a rare bill
14 tables were blown up
four doors, two of them from the living room
of teachers but it is that it was buttoned up with
child is a bill of two thousand 900 euros
I don't understand this Manolo, no.
listen
If you have to go pick me up
car that has a little problem this time
I haven't run out of gas yet.
print
with a children's bus like this, yes
because man man I greet the kids and I
It's confusing, but I have the car.
burst if it is at the gas station yes
where we are always going to eat
San Jaime gas station now if the
very nice kids waving
but my car is broken
see also if not what it feels like in the
soil that is 7 on the ground there are studies
which prove that sitting on the floor
it's hard on the paws
thanks to no one sitting down tell him
Louis get out of my chair [ __ ]
I am vegan okay and if I say yes it is
without milk without milk and on top of that it's happening to me
ready for sugar and I told you
saccharin because it would be Betic then I
It seems disrespectful because I
while I'm saving the turtles from the
sea you are poisoning the
people with milk, that is to say, it is a
serious disrespect if he has left
four tables, eight doors, two of them
from the teachers' lounge loves that is
a bill for three thousand eight hundred euros
It is better to do theater or piano or
anything
also the passion
[Applause]
and
d
ah
then the patient
x
[Applause]
and remember that you have a leak in the
deposit it is best to put tape
insulating
but they have removed me from all classes
the bases that I was explaining here
you are my students
in exchange for class here I don't know how
This works, this is football, well, me
I'm going out because I made a mistake
class or so this is not you are not from
mechanics not from 2nd year mechanical engineering no
OK
and now
[Music]
Hey, is there someone with an open book?
broken into
Sorry, Juan Carlos.
[Music]
that's all
of round ham again but it is that it is
active only but to
further
but it has broken
and there
It is very important that the wheels
[Music]
of classes that you
Gloria please what a disappointment endorsement
Yeah
the versions
two-handed
correct
[Music]
[ __ ] but we have the camera I have
activated
Well, don't be visitors to the last ones
30 years
let's go let's go up
reuters
[Music]
the guard
Yes, I have class, but I have the sample.
disabled
follow
and why did he accept this?
hello
and where you have mistaken him
joint range is resolved therapy
manual to cast that we knew that they are
the strings what these forces do
from the right and vertical traction as
a question
It was about talking about the middle of April.
no
[Music]
It's not something that's going down
and foundations then the risk that
we have you and I and everyone is a little bit
nylon bag
that the wind and the breezes lift them up
instills in you is that you be
that they are
don't touch it
low
[Music]
babies
There is a book that is coming in that is not
It is obviously not what we
we want to have it
-alejandro
further
sorry
minutes
GOOD
you were here
d
although
Yeah
and
and leave family for the yellow fighter
and Tekken through his son Jesus Christ
divine character the kind character
compassionate loving
I'm going to add a tough moment but yes
you are like see five points of that
second was formalized if we follow each other
[Music]
You have the option of GeoGebra
Yeah
what is this
and pastries
but
if it is that
[Laughs]
I have a question, how many ways to
calculate the inverse
[Laughs]
how are we
teacher each question
said richter
END
[Music]
and we are here
most holy day by day
ah
[Music]
they are fine
there they were
GOOD
and continue
Louis, I know, I wear Javier, I know
composed several moments the
elliptical object is the same as the pro
nominal because the subject is explicit
This subject is elliptical which is the hole
okay yes that the to the verb he
It's a bit tacky that one is shouting
to the next thing I imagine that the
The atmosphere in that house is hellish and no
turn off your microphone to see where it is
on the microphone sorry
We are a little nervous about it
We continue confinement if I could sleep
[Applause]
and the dog's all at the end if that is the case
I don't know what kind, shut up
type shut up and remove the mic since it
I have here that is a bore, they won't let me
the microphone that is exhausted by them
but the straw
[Music]
ah
Boys, the capable authorities would be
This is basically important in the game
the very important maximum and gloves I do not
I wear it because I am the teacher who has to
propose and gloves
[Music]
you have to clean the area of a paper well
tin
[Applause]
we clean well
girls this usually happens
Now I do wear gloves because
interested, so we take a break and look
that Professor Marco could explain to me
again the difference between the cells
prokaryotes and eukaryotes is that I have not
It is clear whether there are exams or not.
sorry sorry frame that I dropped
the feline painting
[Music]
The main difference that it has
differences in the exam can
ask directly about the differences
Yes, yes, yes, okay, but someone is going to ask us.
in the safe exam and how much is it worth?
ask
The exam is a 50-point exam.
one hour questions come one hour
file
or not
with all this
1 1
two points away
[Music]
come straight
I said I thought it was off
Sorry, but write to me for a moment.
to the bathroom and think about forgiveness
[Applause]
and
Yeah
sorry
where we find a way to enter
we can give the browser
Hello girls
now
if the girls take a few minutes of rest
very good
This is not the gym class
Aranjuez Municipality
where they visit us
at the dinner table
[Music]
with my mind and bite by [ __ ]
if it is going to be played
[Music]
and it's happening
but
sorry jersey that has fallen a little
There are two classes of yoga, no forgiveness
sorry I'm leaving
left even though my computer is full
of uncle
If you take my computer, don't eat that.
It's full of rum and spaghetti around here
I think I'm in the wrong class like him
link
[Music]